Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Research files
  - Reports
    - Report: Proposed Use of the Third Onondaga Court House, Department of Urban Improvement and the Syracuse Urban Renewal Agency, 1965 (Box 263)
    - Representation of Program Participants, Social Welfare Policy Making: An Analysis of Organization and Participation in an Election Process, O. John Anderson, undated (Box 263)
    - Research report on Crusade for Opportunity employment program, 1965 (Box 263)
    - Research report to employment program, 1965 (Box 263)
    - Statistical, Bi-monthly reports, research, 1966-1967 (Box 263)
    - Statistical reports, data, 1965 (Box 263)
    - Statistics on Negroes in Syracuse, 1966 (Box 263)
    - Summary listings of research project reports, 1967 (Box 263)
    - Syracuse public school enrollment, 1965 (Box 263)
    - United Community Chest and Council of Onondaga County, Inc, Report of the Community Problems Study committee, 1967 (Box 263)
    - Various reports, 1966-1967 (Box 263)
    - Various reports, 1967; 3 folders (Box 264)
  - Staff files
    - Acosta, John files
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 264)
      - Director of Program Development appointment, 1965 (Box 264)
      - Memos, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 264)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 264)
      - Notes, undated (Box 264)
      - Program information, 1965 (Box 264)
    - Armstrong, Lucy files
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 265)
      - Memos, 1967 (Box 265)
      - Notepad, 1967 (Box 265)
    - Burton, William files
      - Memos and flyers, 1967 (Box 265)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967; 5 folders (Box 265)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 266)
    - Cohen, Kenneth files
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 266)
      - Memos, 1967 (Box 266)
    - Fisher, Seth files
      - CAP 5-6-7, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Probation letters, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Prospective research replacements, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Research personnel, 1966 (Box 266)
      - Research staff agenda, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Roster of organizations interested in CFO, undated (Box 266)
      - Youth Development Center, 1964 (Box 266)
      - Youth Development Center contracts, 1963-1965 (Box 266)
    - Glazier, Ruth files, correspondence, 1967; 2 folders (Box 266)
    - Gregory, Ann files, Community Action Memo, 1967 (Box 266)
    - Grey, Lita files, research staff, 1963-1967 (Box 266)
    - Hall, George files
      - Community services, 1966 (Box 266)
      - Data, employment SMA, 1965 (Box 266)
      - Employment forms, 1965 (Box 267)
      - Evaluation of neighborhood survey and election, 1965 (Box 267)
      - Interview schedules, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Miscellaneous reports, 1966 (Box 309)
      - National Council of Aging, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Neighborhood boards, 1965 (Box 267)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1966 (Box 267)
      - OMAT bi-monthly reports, 1964-1965 (Box 267)
      - OEO report, 1965 (Box 267)
      - Staff meetings and internal forms, 1964-1966 (Box 267)
      - Syracuse School District info, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Welfare cases by census tract, 1966 (Box 267)
    - Hill, Dorothy files, Research Division Office Manager
      - Characteristics of Youth in Contact with the Crusade for Opportunity Employment program, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Charles French, Research Aide training, 1967 (Box 267)
      - Claire Weber, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Contents of files, research division, 1967 (Box 267)
      - Daily log, 1967 (Box 267)
      - Deep South, NE, Mid Atlantic, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Demographic survey, 1965 (Box 267)
      - Description of Proposed North Side Area, for commission meeting, 1967 (Box 267)
      - Ditto office supplies, 1966 (Box 267)
      - Feedback sort, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Filing system, 1965 (Box 268)
      - The Field of Action Research Chein, Cook-Harding, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Food Stores by Census Tract, Areas and Volume, R. Glazier, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Forum, more on "Our Illusions about Training," Kenneth Clark, 1966 (Box 268)
      - George Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 268)
      - Gerald Evans - Research Aide training, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Glossary of terms, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Hand guide for community development aides and secretarial staff, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Head Start, Moke Ise, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Help Centers subsequent contact list, 1966 (Box 268)
      - High school equivalency card, 1967 (Box 268)
      - How to use termination form for employment training (form MT-102), OJA, 1966 (Box 268)
      - ID, sex, race, birth, education, action area, etc., Anderson, 1967 (Box 268)
      - An Indepth Probe into Cases Handled led by the CFO Program, OJA - J Stern, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Indexes and Perceptions of Poverty, G Hall, J Indick, J Acosta, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Individual contact cards, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Individual guidance, Ise, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Inez Tremaine, Research Aide trainee, 1965 (Box 268)
      - In-service training expenditures, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Interoffice memos, 1967 (Box 268)
      - Interviewees - paid, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Jack Anderson, crank memos, 1966 (Box 268)
      - Jack Anderson, demographic survey, 1965 (Box 268)
      - Jack Anderson, general typing, 1965 (Box 268)
      - Jack Anderson, general typing, 1966 (Box 269)
      - Jan Marsden, 1965-1966 (Box 269)
      - Job descriptions, 1966 (Box 269)
      - John Benton, neighborhood survey, 1966 (Box 269)
      - John Indick, 1966 (Box 269)
      - John Pelosi, 1966; 2 folders (Box 269)
      - Kathryn Brown - Research Aide training, 1967 (Box 269)
      - Lists of foundations, 1967 (Box 269)
      - Letters written by Jack Anderson, 1966; 2 folders (Box 269)
      - Letters written by Rosenfeld, 1965-1966 (Box 269)
      - Manpower Development Training program, 1967 (Box 269)
      - Marilyn Creel - Research Aide training, 1967 (Box 269)
      - Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 269)
      - Memos by Rosenfeld, 1965-1967 (Box 269)
      - Memos by Jack Anderson, 1965-1966 (Box 270)
      - Memos to Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 270)
      - Memos to John Murray, 1966 (Box 270)
      - National Committee on Employment for Youth, 1965 (Box 270)
      - Neighborhood Board news file, 1965-1966 (Box 270)
      - New York State guidelines, 1965 (Box 270)
      - Not to be considered for employment, 1967 (Box 270)
      - Negro Family Life in America, Billingsley, 1965 (Box 270)
      - OEO proposal, 1966 (Box 270)
      - OEO reports miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 270)
      - Off-set runs, 1966 (Box 270)
      - Old applications, 1966-1967 (Box 270)
      - Old forms not in use, 1966 (Box 270)
      - Problems of Evaluation, Melvin Herman, 1965 (Box 270)
      - Report on 1967 Summer Head Start program, Waldo, Aug 1967 (Box 270)
      - Review of Research Aide applicants, minutes, 1967 (Box 270)
      - Rosenfeld, general typing, 1965-1966 (Box 270)
      - Self-help Among the Poor: New Styles of Social Action, Alinsky in Action, Reissman, undated (Box 270)
      - Social Action on the Installment Plan, George Hall, 1966 (Box 270)
      - A Survey of Alternatives in Acceptable Housing, Ken Cohen, Jul 1967 (Box 270)
      - The Third Force: An Anti-Poverty Ideology, Reisman and Rein, undated (Box 270)
      - Training schedule for research aide program, 1967 (Box 270)
      - Virginia Brown, 1966 (Box 271)
    - Ise, Moko files
      - Coding supervisor, 1966 (Box 271)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1966-1967; 4 folders (Box 271)
      - Data on summer programs, 1966 (Box 271)
      - General typing, 1967 (Box 271)
      - Head Start, 1967 (Box 271)
      - In-service training, 1967 (Box 271)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 271)
      - Miscellaneous memos, 1965 (Box 271)
      - Personnel file, 1966 (Box 271)
      - Reproduction material, 1966 (Box 271)
      - Seminar in NY, 1965 (Box 271)
      - Tables, police file, central registry, welfare, employment, 1967 (Box 272)
      - United Community Chest and Council, 1967 (Box 272)
      - Women's Auxiliary, 1967 (Box 272)
    - Peterson, Sandra files, interview, 1966 (Box 272)
    - Price, Larry files, correspondence, 1966 (Box 272)
    - Rosenfeld, Hilda files, Program Development Specialist
      - A Replay, A. Cloward - R. Ontell, 1965 (Box 272)
      - CAP-20 file, 1966 (Box 272)
      - CFO fact sheets, undated (Box 272)
      - Child daycare centers, statement to Democratic committee, 1966 (Box 272)
      - College work study program, 1966 (Box 272)
      - Community Action forms, 1966 (Box 272)
      - Community Action Program workbook, 1965-1966; 5 folders (Box 272)
      - CORE (Congress on Racial Equality), 1966 (Box 272)
      - Corporation minutes, 1966 (Box 272)
      - Daycare, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Delinquency Prevention Program Study, William H T Smith, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Demographic projections, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Demonstration cities program, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Economic adjustment, 1964-1966 (Box 273)
      - Economic development centers, 1965 (Box 273)
      - Education, 1966; 2 folders (Box 273)
      - Educational opportunity grants, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Educational television, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Employment, case studies, 1966 (Box 273)
      - Employment division, design for evaluation, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Employment program, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Employment proposal, fiscal, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Family Economics Review, 1965 (Box 274)
      - Federal Housing Administration, 1965 (Box 274)
      - Federal Housing Administration, Housing for the Elderly, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Federal resources to support community programs on employment and manpower development, 1965 (Box 274)
      - Female labor market, Syracuse NY, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Female workers, 1965 (Box 274)
      - Finance, 1964 (Box 274)
      - FOCUS, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Foster grandparents, 1965 (Box 274)
      - Funding data, 1967 (Box 274)
      - Handicapped children, education of, 1966 (Box 274)
      - Health, Education, and Welfare
        - Health referral program, 1965 (Box 274)
        - Immunization, 1965 (Box 274)
        - Migrant health, 1966 (Box 275)
        - Miscellaneous materials, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 275)
        - National Technical Institute for the Deaf, 1966 (Box 275)
        - Project grants, 1965-1966 (Box 275)
      - Health, social services, 1966 (Box 275)
      - Home Aides, Inc., community services, 1966-1967 (Box 275)
      - Home Health Aides (Box 275)
        - Home Health Aides, 1966 (Box 275)
        - Draft, 1966 (Box 275)
        - Material resources, 1965-1966 (Box 275)
        - Proposal, 1966 (Box 275)
        - Proposal, working papers, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Task force, 1965 (Box 276)
        - Training program, 1966 (Box 276)
      - Housing checklist of primary sources, 1966 (Box 362)
      - Housing programs (Box 276)
      - Housing, community services, 1966 (Box 276)
      - Housing, miscellaneous materials, 1965-1967 (Box 276)
      - Housing and Urban Development
        - Codes and ordinances, 1965 (Box 276)
        - Community improvement (workable program), 1965 (Box 276)
        - Housing and Home Finance, 1965 (Box 276)
        - Neighborhood facilities, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Press releases and pamphlets, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Rehabilitation, 1965-1966 (Box 276)
        - Robert C. Weaver, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Senior citizens, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Statement to the NYS Joint Legislative committee on HUD, 1966 (Box 276)
        - Urban Planning and Assistance program, undated (Box 276)
        - Urban project transportion, 1965 (Box 276)
        - Urban renewal, 1965 (Box 276)
      - Indian and Eskimo children, undated (Box 276)
      - Indian reservation, 1966 (Box 276)
      - In-service training, 1966-1967 (Box 276)
      - Intra-office correspondence, 1965-1967; 4 folders (Box 277)
      - Job development meeting minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 277)
      - Leased housing, Syracuse, 1965-1966 (Box 277)
      - Leased housing, Washington, 1966 (Box 277)
      - Library memos and materials, 1966 (Box 277)
      - Low income housing, 1966 (Box 277)
      - Manpower Development Training Act (MDTA) correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 277)
      - Maps
        - A, Proposed North Side area, undated (Box 277)
        - B, adjacent areas by census tract, undated (Box 277)
        - All five neighborhood area maps, undated (Box 277)
        - County survey map, undated (Box 277)
        - East Side neighborhood maps, undated (Box 277)
        - Far East side area map, undated (Box 277)
        - Onondaga County and adjacent counties, undated (Box 277)
        - Onondaga County Indian Reservation, undated (Box 277)
        - Syracuse by census tracts, maps, 1955 (Box 277)
        - Tallman neighborhood maps, undated (Box 277)
        - West Side neighborhood map, undated (Box 277)
      - MDT, New York State conferences, 1966 (Box 277)
      - "Mental Health, Social Competence, and the War on Poverty," National Institute of Mental Health, undated (Box 277)
      - Migrant labor, 1965 (Box 277)
      - Migrant workers, 1966 (Box 277)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966; 3 folders (Box 278)
      - Narcotic drug addiction and treatment, 1965 (Box 278)
      - National School Lunch Act, 1964-1965 (Box 278)
      - Negro family life, 1965 (Box 278)
      - "The Negro in Syracuse: His Education, Employment, Income, and Housing," University College of Syracuse University, 1967 (Box 358)
      - Neighborhood board, 1966 (Box 278)
      - Neighborhood legal services, 1966 (Box 278)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps
        - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1965-1966 (Box 278)
        - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 278)
        - Equal Opportunity, 1965-1966 (Box 278)
        - Guidelines, 1966 (Box 279)
        - January report, 1967 (Box 279)
        - Proposal, 1965 (Box 279)
        - Reports submitted, 1966 (Box 279)
      - New York City's Human Resources, 1966 (Box 279)
      - New York State housing, 1966 (Box 279)
      - North High School, 1965 (Box 279)
      - Notes of CFO staff minutes, 1967 (Box 279)
      - Nursing education, 1964-1966 (Box 279)
      - Office for the Aging, 1966 (Box 279)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity
        - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965 (Box 279)
        - Amendments, 1967 (Box 279)
        - Application forms, 1965 (Box 279)
        - CAP 20 forms, 1966-1967 (Box 279)
        - CAP memos, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 280)
        - Checkpoint procedures, 1966 (Box 280)
        - Curriculum Materials Development Center, 1965 (Box 280)
        - Education components, 1965-1966 (Box 280)
        - Elderly-Foster Grandparent Program expansion, 1966 (Box 280)
        - Financial, 1965 (Box 280)
        - Fiscal, 1966 (Box 280)
        - Fiscal proposal, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 280)
        - Fiscal - war on poverty budget, 1967 (Box 280)
        - Funding, fiscal background, 1967 (Box 280)
        - FY 1968 projections, 1967 (Box 280)
        - Memorandums, 1966-1967 (Box 280)
        - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 281)
        - New York State, 1967 (Box 281)
        - Pamphlets, 1966 (Box 281)
        - Program status report, 1965-1967; 18 folders (Box 281)
        - Proposal fiscal, notes (Box 281)
        - Proposal guidelines, 1964-1966 (Box 281)
        - Special data, 1966 (Box 282)
        - Special report, 1965-1966 (Box 282)
        - Title V, work experience program, 1967 (Box 282)
      - Office of Manpower, Automation, and Training
        - OMAT, 1964-1967; 4 folders (Box 282)
        - Basic data reports, 1965-1966 (Box 282)
        - Bi-monthly report, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 282)
        - Employment data, 1965 (Box 282)
        - Los Angeles, 1964 (Box 282)
        - Los Angeles, 1965 (Box 283)
        - Proposal - Appalachia, California, 1965 (Box 283)
        - Proposal - Syracuse, 1964 (Box 283)
        - Reports (copies), 1965-1966 (Box 283)
        - Reports - Arizona, 1965 (Box 283)
      - Onondaga Health Department, health proposal, 1967 (Box 283)
      - Payroll control data, OEO, 1965; 2 folders (Box 283)
      - Performing acts facility program, 1966 (Box 283)
      - Personnel, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 283)
      - Pittsburgh, 1966 (Box 283)
      - Potent organizations, 1965 (Box 283)
      - Poverty profile: "Syracuse Faces its Youth Unemployment Problems," The WE Upjohn Institute for Employment Research, 1965 (Box 283)
      - Powell Committee report, 1965 (Box 283)
      - Presidents Committee for Juvenile Delinquency, research information, 1966 (Box 284)
      - Program progress report, 1966-1967 (Box 284)
      - Proposals, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 284)
      - Reproduction, 1966 (Box 284)
      - Research, 1965-1967 (Box 284)
      - Senior staff, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 284)
      - Senior staff minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 284)
      - Shriver scholarships, 1966 (Box 362)
      - South Side neighborhood, 1966 (Box 285)
      - Summer tutorial assistance program, Syracuse, NY, 1967 (Box 285)
      - Syracuse housing, 1964-1966 (Box 285)
      - Syracuse Housing Authority, 1966 (Box 285)
      - TAPS, 1967
      - Technical assistance, NYS OEO, 1966 (Box 285)
      - Theatre programs, 1966 (Box 285)
      - To read, 1967 (Box 358)
      - Tutorial summer, 1967 (Box 285)
      - Upward Bound (LeMoyne HEP), 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of Agriculture, extension service, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of Agriculture, rural programs, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of Agriculture, US Food Stamp Program, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of Commerce, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of Commerce, Economic Development Administration, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US Department of the Interior, 1966 (Box 285)
      - US surplus personal property, 1966 (Box 286)
      - Veterans, 1965-1966 (Box 286)
    - Tolley, Gail files, memo, 1966 (Box 286)
    - Wenkert, Robert files, correspondence regarding requests for articles or being placed on mailing lists, 1965 (Box 286)
    - Wenkert, Robert files, memos to Jack Anderson, 1965 (Box 286)
  - Surveys
    - Community Action Program information survey, 1967 (Box 286)
    - Community services feedback, 1965-1967 (Box 286)
    - Community survey sample, 1966 (Box 286)
    - Community workers skill questionnaire, 1967 (Box 286)
    - Confidential questionnaire, 1966 (Box 286)
    - Consumer survey, 1966 (Box 286)
    - Consumer survey actions, 1966-1967 (Box 286)
    - County survey, 1966 (Box 286)
    - County survey area report selected area in East Syracuse, 1967 (Box 286)
    - Data and analysis from Syracuse neighborhood survey, 1966 (Box 286)
    - Data table, undated (Oversize 1)
    - Demographic survey, Jack Anderson, 1965 (Box 286)
    - Neighborhood consumer survey, 1967; 2 folders (Box 286)
    - Neighborhood housing surveys, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood housing survey, action area, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood housing surveys, Far East, East, West, North, Tallman, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood questionnaire, youth's opinions of Crusade, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey, 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey answers, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey info for sorts (blank forms), 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey interview schedule, 1966 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey marginals, 1966 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey, open end questions, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Neighborhood survey, open end questions, 1967 (Box 362)
    - NYS employment service survey of unemployed youths, 1965 (Box 287)
    - Opinion poll, Moko Ise, undated (Box 287)
    - Participants in school by each Study Center, 1966 (Box 287)
    - Questionnaire, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Questionnaire regarding programs, 1965 (Box 287)
    - Statistical data, bi-monthly reports, 1967 (Box 287)
    - Statistics on neighborhood survey, circa 1966 (Box 287)
    - Street survey, house conditions, North Side, Jun 1967 (Box 287)
    - A survey of alternatives in acceptable housing, Kenneth E Cohen, 1967 (Box 287)
    - A survey of training opportunities for Syracuse University rehabilitation counselor trainees at the Crusade for Opportunity, 1965 (Box 288)
    - Syracuse neighborhood survey, undated (Box 288)
    - Syracuse neighborhood survey, Betty Baer, 1963 (Box 362)
    - Syracuse neighborhood survey, blank, OJA, undated (Box 288)
    - Syracuse neighborhood survey, typing draft, 1965; 2 folders (Box 288)
    - Youth Development Center, Syracuse Youth Opinion poll, Syracuse neighborhood survey, forms, Jul 1963 (Box 362)
- General correspondence-subject files
  - Correspondence and subject files
    - Action for Appalachian Youth, 1965 (Box 358)
    - Chicago Committee on Urban Opportunity, 1966 (Box 288)
    - Citizen's Council on Urban Renewal, 1965 (Box 288)
    - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty, 1964-1966 (Box 288)
    - City of Syracuse, Parks and Recreation, 1967 (Box 358)
    - Control Syracuse Bulletin, 1964 (Box 288)
    - CORE, 1964 (Box 288)
    - Council of Churches, 1965-1966 (Box 288)
    - County of Onondaga, budgets, 1966 (Box 358)
    - County of Onondaga, Department of Public Works, 1966 (Box 358)
    - CUNA International, Inc., 1967 (Box 288)
    - CUNY, 1966 (Box 288)
    - Eric Mower, 1967 (Box 288)
    - Frank Piskar, Vice President of Academic Affairs, Syracuse University, 1962-1965; 4 folders (Box 288)
    - Frank Piskar, Vice President of Academic Affairs, Syracuse University, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 289)
    - Frank Piskar, Vice President of Academic Affairs, Syracuse University, Middle States, 1966; 4 folders (Box 289)
    - Frank Piskar, Vice President of Academic Affairs, Syracuse University, Middle States, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Jacob K. Javits, United States Senate, 1966 (Box 362)
    - March on Washington, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Mayor's Commission on Human Rights, A General Ordinance Creating a Mayor's Commission on Human Rights, 1961 (Box 362)
    - Mayor William Walsh, State of the City speech, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Medicare, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Medicare, 1966 (Box 359)
    - National Association for Community Development, 1967 (Box 290)
    - National Committee for Children and Youth, 1965 (Box 290)
    - New Jersey Community Action Training Tenant Action, pamphlet, 1966 (Box 290)
    - New York City Council Against Poverty, 1967 (Box 290)
    - New York State Department of Labor, 1965 (Box 359)
    - Nicholson and Robinson, 1965-1966 (Box 359)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, newsletters and correspondence, 1967; 2 folders (Box 290)
    - Older American Act, 1966 (Box 359)
    - Organizations of Organizations, undated (Box 290)
    - Organizations of Organizations, 1966 (Box 362)
    - People's Organization to Win Equal Rights, constitution, undated (Box 359)
    - Pollution, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Profile for Industry, Camillus, NY, undated (Box 359)
    - Small Business Administration, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Small Business Development Center, 1965-1966 (Box 359)
    - Social Service Committee of Urban Renewal Citizens Council, 1964-1965 (Box 359)
    - State Charities and Association, 1966 (Box 290)
    - Syracuse Area Council of Churches, undated; 2 folders (Box 290)
    - Syracuse City School District, Board of Education, 1965 (Box 359)
    - Syracuse Committee for Integrated Education, undated (Box 290)
    - Syracuse Community Development Association, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 291)
    - Syracuse Community Nursery School, 1967 (Box 291)
    - Syracuse Housing Authority, 1966 (Box 291)
    - Syracuse University, 1965-1966 (Box 291)
    - Syracuse University, Computing Center, 1960; 2 folders (Box 291)
    - Syracuse University, School of Social Work, 1964 (Box 291)
    - Syracuse University, Technical Resources Center, 1967 (Box 291)
    - Syracuse University, Youth Development Center, 1963 (Box 291)
    - Technology Club of Syracuse, 1967 (Box 291)